LEONARD: What does that mean?
- Nothing.
You seem to be implying a back channel
between me and Penny...
(Sheldon:)- ...where, obviously, none exists.
- No, I didn't.
(Sheldon:)I just think you need to be careful
how you phrase things, sir.
- What's going on with you?
- Well, I might ask you the same question.
Why do you drag me into matters
which have nothing to do with me...
(Sheldon:)...but exist between you and Penny,
a person to whom I barely speak?
(Leonard:)What's wrong with your face?
(Sheldon:)There's no reason
to bring my looks into this.
(Sheldon:)- Good day, Leonard.
- What?
(Sheldon:)I said, good day.
(Leonard:)Good day?
(Penny:)Also today we have
a fresh-caught Alaska salmon...
(Penny:)...served with a teriyaki glaze
and sticky rice.